- You might've heard
that people may forget what you said and what you did,
but they'll never forget how you made them feel.
I'm paraphrasing a quote from Maya Angelou,
but it applies perfectly to social selling.
Prospective customers want to feel special.
Like individuals, not just another client.
If you can create this feeling,
sales success will be more likely to follow.
When we treat people as individuals
and communicate with them in ways that convey respect,
it's amazing the difference it can make on a professional
and personal level.
The goal of this course
is to help you enjoy more sales success.
When you combine an understanding
of the psychology of persuasion and personality styles,
success will come quicker and more often.
I'm Brian Ahearn,
and I've been teaching salespeople, coaches,
business leaders and others
how to ethically influence people for the past 15 years.
In this course you'll learn three very important things
when it comes to selling your products, services or ideas.
First, you'll be introduced
to some basic psychological concepts
that will make it easier for people to say yes to you.
Next, you'll learn how to quickly identify
different personality types.
Finally, and most important,
you'll see which psychological concepts work best
with each personality style.
Are you ready to make that happen?
Let's get started.